Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Other Play Photographs and Negatives, circa 1944-2004; D
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (9 of 12) (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (10 of 12) (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (11 of 12) (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (12 of 12) (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (1 of 9) (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (2 of 9) (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (3 of 9) (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (4 of 9) (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (5 of 9) (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (6 of 9) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (7 of 9) (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (8 of 9) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1974-2004; (9 of 9) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Other Play Negatives, circa 1974-2004; (1 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Other Play Negatives, circa 1974-2004; (2 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Other Play Negatives, circa 1974-2004; (3 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Other Play Negatives, circa 1974-2004; (4 of 4) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Hunter Hills, 1966-1977; E
    - Hunter Hills Season Brochures, 1966-1977 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Annie Get Your Gun, 1966 July; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Annie Get Your Gun, 1967 July; (Photographs) (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Carousel, 1967 June-September; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1967 June-September; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Camelot, 1968 July-September; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1968 July-September; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1969 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Li'l Abner, 1969 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1970 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Li'l Abner, 1970 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Oklahoma!, 1970 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1971 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Oklahoma!, 1971 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - The Sound of Music, 1971 July-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Hello Dolly!, 1972 June-August; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clipping) (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Hello Dolly!, 1972 June-August; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1972 June-September; (1 of 2); (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Dark of the Moon, (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1972 July-August; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clipping) (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1972 July-August; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1973; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Hello Dolly!, 1973 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - The Wizard of Oz, 1973 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1974 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - South Pacific, 1974 June-August; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - South Pacific, 1974 June-August; (2 of 2); (Negatives) (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Camelot, 1975 July-September; (Photographs) (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Camelot, 1975 December 11-14; (1 of 2); (Playbill and Press Clippings) (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Camelot, 1975 December 11-14; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Smoke on the Mountains, 1977 June-August; (Playbill) (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Other Hunter Hills Productions, undated; (Playbills) (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Press Clippings (Miscellaneous Productions), circa 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Play Photographs (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977; (1 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Play Photographs (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977; (2 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Play Photographs (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977; (3 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Play Photographs (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977; (4 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Play Photographs (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977; (5 of 5) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Play Negatives (Miscellaneous), circa 1967-1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Students Association and Other UT Productions, 1978 July-1988 April 17; F
    - Summer Company ( The Grass Harp; The Threepenny Opera; Happy Birthday Wanda June), 1978 July-August; (Playbills) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Lady Windermer's Fan; The Mandrake; Mr. Roosevelt's Train; The Father), 1980 July-August; (1 of 2); (Playbills, PSAs, and Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Lady Windermer's Fan; The Mandrake; Mr. Roosevelt's Train; The Father), 1980 July-August; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( The Master Builder; King Ubu; Huck), 1981 July-August; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( The Master Builder; King Ubu; Huck), 1981 July-August; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Equus; The Rivals; Three Sisters), 1984 July-August; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Equus; The Rivals; Three Sisters), 1984 July-August; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( H.M.S. Pinafore; You Can't Take It With You; The Hollow), 1985 July-August; (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Crimes of the Heart; Spoon River; The Misanthrope), 1986 July-August; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Summer Classics Repetory ( Crimes of the Heart; Spoon River; The Misanthrope), 1986 July-August; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1987 May 21-24; (Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Old Times, circa September 1987; (Press Clipping) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - All Night Theatre Festival, 1988 February 20; (Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Picnic, 1988 April 14-17; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings) (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Picnic, 1988 April 14-17; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Holiday, 2005 November 10-20; (Playbill) (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Agnes of God, undated; (Playbill) (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Other UT Productions, circa 1985; (Playbills and PSAs) (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - AV Materials, circa 1972-2002 October 27; G
    - The Heidi Chronicles (Performance), 1991 October 11-27; (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 1)
    - A Christmas Carol, 1991 November 22-December 22; (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 2)
    - The Mandrake (Performance), 1992 October 2-16; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 39, Cassette 3)
    - The Mandrake (Performance), 1992 October 2-16; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 39, Cassette 4)
    - Liliom (Performance), 1993 April 16-May 2; (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 5)
    - 1940s Radio Hour (Performance), 1993 November 19-December 12; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 1) (Box 39, Cassette 6)
    - 1940s Radio Hour (Performance), 1993 November 19-December 12; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 2) (Box 39, Cassette 7)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel, Act I (Performance), 1994 October 14-29; (1 of 2); (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 8)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel, Act II (Performance), 1994 October 14-29; (2 of 2); (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 9)
    - A Christmas Carol (Performance), 1994 November 25-December 21; (On VHS) (Box 39, Cassette 10)
    - Grapes of Wrath (Performance), 1995 February 3-15; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 1) (Box 39, Cassette 11)
    - Grapes of Wrath (Performance), 1995 February 3-15; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 2) (Box 39, Cassette 12)
    - Ajax/Hero's No Fool (Performance), 1995 May 1; (On VHS) (Box 40, Cassette 1)
    - Grease, Act I (Performance), 1996 October 11-27; (1 of 4); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 2)
    - Grease, Act II (Performance), 1996 October 11-27; (2 of 4); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 3)
    - Grease, Act I (Performance), 1996 October 11-27; (3 of 4); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 40, Cassette 4)
    - Grease, Act II (Performance), 1996 October 11-27; (4 of 4); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 40, Cassette 5)
    - Grease, Act I (Performance-Evening Cast), 1996 October 11-27; (1 of 4); (On VHS; Evening Cast - Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 6)
    - Grease, Act II (Performance-Evening Cast), 1996 October 11-27; (2 of 4); (On VHS; Evening Cast - Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 7)
    - Grease, Act I (Performance-Evening Cast), 1996 October 11-27; (3 of 4); (On VHS; Evening Cast - Copy 2) (Box 40, Cassette 8)
    - Grease, Act II (Performance-Evening Cast), 1996 October 11-27; (4 of 4); (On VHS; Evening Cast - Copy 2) (Box 40, Cassette 9)
    - Andorra (Performance), 1997 March 11-22; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 10)
    - Andorra (Performance), 1997 March 11-22; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 40, Cassette 11)
    - Catfish Moon (Performance), 1999 August 27-September 11; (On VHS) (Box 40, Cassette 12)
    - Hamlet (Performance), 2000 March 9-12; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 40, Cassette 13)
    - Hamlet (Performance), 2000 March 9-12; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 41, Cassette 1)
    - The Rainmaker (Performance), 2001 August 31-September 15; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 41, Cassette 2)
    - The Rainmaker (Performance), 2001 August 31-September 15; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 41, Cassette 3)
    - Three Sisters (Performance), 2002 March 1-16; (1 of 4); (On VHS; Tape 1; Copy 1) (Box 41, Cassette 4)
    - Three Sisters (Performance), 2002 March 1-16; (2 of 4); (On VHS; Tape 2; Copy 1) (Box 41, Cassette 5)
    - Three Sisters (Performance), 2002 March 1-16; (3 of 4); (On VHS; Tape 1; Copy 2) (Box 41, Cassette 6)
    - Three Sisters (Performance), 2002 March 1-16; (4 of 4); (On VHS; Tape 2; Copy 2) (Box 41, Cassette 7)
    - All in the Timing (Performance), 2002 May 31-June 15; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 1) (Box 41, Cassette 8)
    - All in the Timing (Performance), 2002 May 31-June 15; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Tape 2) (Box 41, Cassette 9)
    - Nora (Performance), 2002 October 11-27; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 41, Cassette 10)
    - Nora (Performance), 2002 October 11-27; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 41, Cassette 11)
    - Arcadia (Rehearsal), 2000 September 1-17; (On VHS) (Box 41, Cassette 12)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train; Blood Wedding; Into the Woods (Commercials), 1991 February 1-16; (On VHS) (Box 41, Cassette 13)
    - When the Nightengale Sings (Commercials), 1991 September 6-22; (On VHS) (Box 41, Cassette 14)
      (Commercial features Alex Haley)
    - Twelfth Night (Commercials), 1992 March 6-21; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 1)
    - Royal Hunt for the Sun and Diablomundo (Commercials), 1994 April 11; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 2)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Commercials), 1994 May 20; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 3)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel; A Christmas Carol (Commercials), 1994 October 14-29; November 25-December 21; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 4)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Commercials), 1995 May 5-20; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 5)
    - They're Playing Our Song (Commercials), 2000 April 14-29; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 6)
    - The Moving of Lilla Barton (Commercials), 2000 June 2-17; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 42, Cassette 7)
    - The Moving of Lilla Barton (Commercials), 2000 June 2-17; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 42, Cassette 8)
    - Arcadia (Commercials), 2000 September 1-17; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 9)
    - Woman in Black (Commercials), 2000 October 13-28; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 10)
    - Inherit the Wind (Commercials), 2001 February 2; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 42, Cassette 11)
    - Inherit the Wind (Commercials), 2001 February 2; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 42, Cassette 12)
    - The Brecht File (Commercials), 2001 March 7; (On VHS) (Box 42, Cassette 13)
    - The Glass Menagerie (Commercials), 2001 April 13-28; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 1)
    - Hunter Hills (Documentary), circa 1972; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 2)
      (Documentary features Fred Fields)
    - 20th Anniversary of the Clarence Brown Theatre (Party Footage), 1990 November 11; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 43, Cassette 3)
    - 20th Anniversary of the Clarence Brown Theatre (Party Footage), 1990 November 11; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 43, Cassette 4)
    - Diablomundo/Copia V (Isadores)/African Dances, circa 1992; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 5)
    - Diablomundo Residency, circa 1993-1994; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 6)
    - Diablomundo Workshop (CBT/MFA), circa 1994; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 7)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre/Diablomundo Collaboration, circa 1994; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 8)
    - Royal Hunt for the Sun with Diablomundo (Performance), 1994 April 27; (On VHS) (Box 43, Cassette 9)
    - James Moran Memorial, 1994 October 10; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 43, Cassette 10)
    - James Moran Memorial, 1994 October 10; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 43, Cassette 11)
    - The Dr. and Mrs. A.H. Lancaster Library Friends Lecture Featuring John O'Keefe, 1997 March 4; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 43, Cassette 12)
    - The Dr. and Mrs. A.H. Lancaster Library Friends Lecture Featuring John O'Keefe, 1997 March 4; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 43, Cassette 13)
    - John Ferguson Reads A Christmas Carol, circa December 1998; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 1)
    - Julie Harris Reading, undated; (1 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 1) (Box 44, Cassette 2)
    - Julie Harris Reading, undated; (2 of 2); (On VHS; Copy 2) (Box 44, Cassette 3)
    - Netherlands/US Touring Exchange Project, undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 4)
    - National Theatre of Bashkortostan, undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 5)
    - Object Theatre Workshop (Performance), undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 6)
    - Tennessee Dance Theatre, undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 7)
    - Marian Brown Portrait Unveiling, 1990 October 11; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 8)
    - Bingham Group LLC (Demo), undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 9)
    - RehearScores (Demo), undated; (On VHS) (Box 44, Cassette 10)
    - Maxwell KCS20 Umatic Mini Cassette (unlabeled), undated; (On Umatic Mini Cassette) (Box 44, Cassette 11)
    - Emtec Betcam SP Cassette (unlabeled), undated; (On Betacam Cassette) (Box 44, Cassette 12)
    - Our Town (Radio PSA), 1975 March 5-15; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 1)
    - Amadeus (Radio PSA), 1988 September 9-24; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 2)
    - A Salute to Clarence Brown (Presentation), 1990 November; (On Umatic Video Tape) (Box 45, Cassette 3)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Radio PSA), 1991 February 1-16; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 4)
    - Blood Wedding (Radio PSA), 1991 February 13; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 5)
    - Into the Woods (Radio PSA), 1991 May 30-June 15; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 6)
    - 1776 (TV PSA), 1992 April 10-26; (On 3M Reel-to-Reel Video Tape) (Box 45, Reel 7)
    - A Man for all Seasons (Radio PSA), 1992 September 11-October 3; (1 of 2); (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 8)
    - A Man for all Seasons (TV PSA), 1992 September 11-October 3; (2 of 2); (On 3M Reel-to-Reel Video Tape) (Box 45, Reel 9)
    - Oliver (Radio PSA), 1992 November 20-December 13; (1 of 2); (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 10)
    - Oliver (TV PSA), 1992 November 20-December 13; (2 of 2); (On Ampex Umatic Cassette) (Box 45, Cassette 11)
    - Dracula, Prince of the Dark (PSA), 1995 March 23; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 12)
    - Arcadia (Radio PSA), 2000 September 1-17; (On CD) (Box 45, Disk 13)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), undated; (On Reel-to-Reel Audiotape) (Box 45, Reel 14)
    - UT Theatres (Radio PSA), undated; (On 8-Track Tape) (Box 45, Cassette 15)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 1, circa April 1994; (1 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 1)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 2, circa April 1994; (2 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 2)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 3, circa April 1994; (3 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 3)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 4, circa April 1994; (4 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 4)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 5, circa April 1994; (5 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 5)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Rehearsal) -- Tape 6, circa April 1994; (6 of 6); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 6)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun Carpetbag Workshop, circa April 1994; (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 7)
    - Carpetbag Theatre (Rehearsal), circa April 1994; (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 8)
    - Grease, Act I (Performance), circa October 1996; (1 of 2); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 9)
    - Grease, Act II (Performance), circa October 1996; (2 of 2); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 10)
    - Catfish Moon, circa August 1999; (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 11)
    - An O. Henry Christmas (Performance), 1999 December 15; (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 12)
    - Untitled Play, Thursday Performance, Act I, undated; (1 of 2); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 13)
    - Untitled Play, Thursday Performance, Act II, undated; (2 of 2); (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 14)
    - 8mm Video Cassette (unlabeled), undated; (On 8mm Video) (Box 46, Cassette 15)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), circa December 1985; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 1)
    - The Lion in Winter (Radio PSA), circa February 1986; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 2)
    - Bus Stop (Radio PSA), circa May 1986; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 3)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Radio PSA), circa November 1989; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 4)
    - Steel Magnolias (Radio PSA), 1990 September 25; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 5)
    - Steel Magnolias (Radio PSA), 1990 September 26; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 6)
    - Steel Magnolias (Radio PSA), circa 1990 September; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 7)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Radio PSA), 1990 October 8; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 8)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird (Radio PSA), 1990 October 22; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 9)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), 1990 November 1; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 10)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), 1990 November 15; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 11)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), 1990 November 22; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 12)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Radio PSA), 1991 January 25; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 13)
    - Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (Radio PSA), 1991 February 5; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 14)
    - Blood Wedding (Radio PSA), 1991 February 19; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 15)
    - Skin of Our Teeth (Radio PSA), 1991 April 4; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 16)
    - When the Nightingale Sings (Radio PSA), 1991 August 29; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 17)
    - The Heidi Chronicles (Radio PSA), 1991 October 7; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 18)
    - A Christams Carol (Radio PSA), 1991 November 18; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 19)
    - Twelfth Night (Radio PSA), circa 1992 March; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 20)
    - 1776 (Radio PSA), 1992 March 31; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 21)
    - Lilliom (Radio PSA), 1993 April 16-May 2; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 22)
    - I Hate Hamlet (Radio PSA), 1993 August 27-September 12; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 23)
    - Cowboy Comedy of Errors (Radio PSA), 1993 October 1-17; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 47, Cassette 24)
    - 1940s Radio Hour (Radio PSA), 1993 November 19-December 12; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 1)
    - Our Country's Good (Radio PSA), 1994 February 4-20; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 2)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun (Radio PSA), 1994 April 15-May 1; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 3)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (Radio PSA), 1994 May 27-June 24; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 4)
    - Grapes of Wrath (Radio PSA), 1995 February 3-15; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 5)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Radio PSA), 1995 March 31-April 15; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 6)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Radio PSA), 1995 October 13-29; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 7)
    - The Country Wife (Radio PSA), 1996 February 23-March 9; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 8)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), 1996 November 19; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 9)
    - Andorra (Radio PSA), 1997 February 28; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 10)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Radio PSA), 1997 April 10-May 3; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 11)
    - Untitled Clarence Brown Theatre Radio Spot, 1997 June 12; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 12)
    - Terra Nova (Radio PSA), 1997 August 22; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 13)
    - Shadow of the Vampire (Radio PSA), 1998 January 30-February 14; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 14)
    - The Seagull (Radio PSA), 1998 February 27-March 13; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 15)
    - Fiddler on the Roof (Radio PSA), 1998 April 10-25; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 16)
    - Fred Curchack's Stuff as Dreams are Made On (Radio PSA), 1998 May 7-8; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 17)
    - Dancing at Lughnasa (Radio PSA), 1998 June 5-20; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 18)
    - Dance in Time (Radio PSA), 1998 August 28-September 13; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 19)
    - A Christmas Carol (Radio PSA), 1998 November 20-December 11; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 20)
    - 1991-1992 Season (Radio PSA), 1991 May 10; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 21)
    - 1992-1993 Season (Radio PSA), 1992 May 11; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 22)
    - 1993-1994 Season (Radio PSA), 1993 May 19; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 23)
    - 1993-1994 Season (Radio PSA), 1993 August 27; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 48, Cassette 24)
    - Bill Coleman Interview on Knoxview, 1991 August 25; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 49, Cassette 1)
    - Blood Wedding (Music), 1991; (1 of 2); (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 49, Cassette 2)
    - Blood Wedding (Music), 1991; (2 of 2); (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 49, Cassette 3)
    - Prince of the Dark (Music), circa 1994 August; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 49, Cassette 4)
    - Dracula (Music), 1994 August; (On Compact [Audio] Cassette) (Box 49, Cassette 5)